Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      Series contains vinyl discs that are either not annotated or the annotations are small and were missed during the sorting of discs. While some effort was taken to bring together piences that were dense in copy-specific track preferences. These items are arranged in alphabetical order by artists’ last name or the name of the group. Each letter of the alphabet has a subseries. Compilations, soundtracks, and other albums with various artists are in subseries together. Artists and groups whose names start with a number are in a separate subseries. Most artists are alphabetized under the name they are most well-known as (e.g. Puff Daddy; Prince; Fela). The variations of names are contained in the Creator field. In a few cases, however, artists’ aliases were unknown, and they may have been listed under two different artist names.
      - N
        - N-Phase - Spend the night, 1994; SR-22651; N-Phase (Box 368)
          Promo
          Catalog # PRO-A-6834; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-6834-SR1
          Maverick
          Burbank, California
        - N-Toon - Ready, 1999; SR-22652; N-Toon (Box 368)
          Catalog # DRM8P-5275; A-side Matrix # DRM8P-5275-A
          DreamWorks Records
          Universal City, California
        - N-Trance - Da ya think I'm sexy?, 1997; SR-22653; N-Trance; Stewart, Rod (Box 368)
          Catalog # 12DJ GLOBE 150; A-side Matrix # 12-DJ-GLOBE-150-A
          All Around The World
          Blackburn, United Kingdom
        - N-Trance - Stayin' alive; Set U free, 1995; SR-22654; N-Trance (Box 368)
          Catalog # RU15050; A-side Matrix # RU-15050-A
          Radikal Records
          Teaneck, New Jersey
        - N2DEEP - The weekend; V-town, 1993; SR-22655; N2DEEP (Box 368)
          Catalog # PRO-7395; A-side Matrix # PRO-7395-A
          Profile Records
          New York, New York
        - N2DEEP - California hot tubs, 1995; SR-22656; N2DEEP (Box 368)
          Catalog # 94590-1; A-side Matrix # 94590-1-A S-30794
          Bust It Records
          Oakland, California
        - Nadanuf - The breaks, 1996; SR-22657; Nadanuf (Box 368)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8920; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8920/A-SR1
          Reprise Records
        - Nails - Hotel for women, 1981; SR-22658; Nails (Box 368)
          Catalog # CJN-111-1; A-side Matrix # CJN-111-1
          Jimboco Records
        - Nails, Danny - You are the only one, 1988; SR-22659; Nails, Danny (Box 368)
          Catalog # HL 1001; A-side Matrix # HL-1001-A
          Harbor Light Records
        - Nairobi - Funky soul makossa, 1982; SR-22660; Nairobi; Awesome Foursome; Dibango, Manu (Box 368)
          In same jacket as # SR-22681. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # SWRL-2205-A; A-side Matrix # SWRL-2205-A
          Streetwise
        - Nairobi - Funky soul makossa, 1982; SR-22681; Nairobi; Awesome Foursome (Box 368)
          In same jacket as # SR-22660. 2 copies.Promo
        - Nais - 69B (Alizè & me), 1995; SR-22661; Nais (Box 368)
          Catalog # SBAB 78046-1; A-side Matrix # SBAB-78046-1-A S-32224
          Scotti Bros. Records
          Santa Monica, California
        - Najee - Tokyo blue, 1990; SR-22662; Najee (Box 368)
          Catalog # E1-92248; A-side Matrix # E1-1-92248-22-DMM SP1-1
          EMI
          Hollywood, California
        - Najee - I'll be good to you, 1990; SR-22663; Najee (Box 368)
          In same jacket as # SR-22682. Different discs.
          Catalog # SPRO 04614; A-side Matrix # SPRO-04614-Z1
          EMI USA
        - Love, Monie - It's a shame (my sister), 1990; SR-22682; Love, Monie; True Image (Box 368)
          In same jacket as # SR-22663. Different discs.
          Catalog # COOLX 219-A; A-side Matrix # COOLX 219 A-1J-1-1
          Cooltempo
          London, United Kingdom
        - Naked Eyes - (What) in the name of love, 1984; SR-22664; Naked Eyes (Box 368)
          Catalog # V-7832-1; A-side Matrix # V17832-24
          EMI America
        - Nami - On the street, 1984; SR-22665; Nami (Box 368)
          Catalog # JAZ7773; A-side Matrix # JAZ 001LA
          Jamaazima
          Bronx, New York
        - Napoli - Malas prontas; Aquela loka; Com amor, 2006; SR-22667; Napoli (Box 368)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # AA000300/1006-63A
          Cash Beat Records
          Brazil
        - Napoli Centrale - Napoli centrale, 1975; SR-22668; Napoli Centrale (Box 368)
          Catalog # SMRL 6159; A-side Matrix # S-6159
          Ricordi
          Italy
        - Napoli Centrale - Mattanza, 1976; SR-22669; Napoli Centrale (Box 368)
          Catalog # SMRL 6187; A-side Matrix # S-6187-1
        - Napoli, Jeanne - Lets make love, 1977; SR-22670; Napoli, Jeanne (Box 368)
          DJ Copy
          Catalog # VI-D 734; A-side Matrix # VI-D734-A
          Vigor Records
        - Nappy Headz - Robbery, 1998; SR-22671; Nappy Headz (Box 368)
          Not in discogs
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # NAPPY HEADZ-A
          Music World Rap Omni Music
          Florida, United States
        - Naptron - Put your hands up, 2000; SR-22672; Naptron (Box 368)
          Catalog # 006; A-side Matrix # 006-A
          Funk La Planet
        - Narada - Divine emotions, 1988; SR-22673; Narada (Box 368)
          Catalog # 0-20874; A-side Matrix # 0-20874-A
        - Nas - Street dreams (remix), 1996; SR-22674; Nas; Kelly, R. (Box 368)
          Catalog # CAS 9205; A-side Matrix # XSS-9205-A
          Columbia
        - Nas - If I ruled the world, 1996; SR-22675; Nas (Box 368)
          In same jacket as # SR-22666. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 44 78327; A-side Matrix # XSS 78327A-1B
        - Nas - If I ruled the world, 1996; SR-22666; Nas (Box 368)
          In same jacket as # SR-22675. 2 copies.
        - Nas - Street dreams, 1996; SR-22676; Nas; AZ; Cormega; Brown, Foxy (Box 368)
          In same jacket as # SR-22683. Different discs.
          Catalog # 44 78408; A-side Matrix # XSS 78408A-1A
        - Heather B. - Takin mine; My kinda n*gga, 1996; SR-22683; Heather B. (Box 368)
          In same jacket as # SR-22676. Different discs.Promo
          Catalog # SPRO-11620; A-side Matrix # 7087-6-11620-1-1B1
        - Nas - You won’t see me tonight; We will survive, 1999; SR-22677; Nas (Box 368)
          Catalog # CAS 42461; A-side Matrix # XSS-42461-A-1
        - Nas - Nas is like; Dr. Knockboots, 1999; SR-22678; Nas (Box 368)
          Catalog # 44 79113; A-side Matrix # XSS-79113-A2
        - Nas - Made you look (remix), 2003; SR-22679; Nas; Jadakiss; Ludacris (Box 368)
          Catalog # ZZ-105; A-side Matrix # ZZ-105-A
          United States
        - Nas - The foulness & freestyle, 1996; SR-22680; Nas (Box 368)
          Catalog # NAS FRE 2; A-side Matrix # NAS-FRE-2A
        - Nas - Half time, 1992; SR-22684; Nas; Nasty Nas (Box 368)
          Catalog # 44 74777; A-side Matrix # XSS-74777A-1A
          Ruffhouse Records ‎
        - Nas - Hate me now, 1999; SR-22685; Nas; Puff Daddy; Diddy; Nature (Box 368)
          Catalog # 44 79070; A-side Matrix # XSS-79070-A-1
        - Nas - Nastradamus; Shoot 'em up, 1999; SR-22686; Nas (Box 368)
          Catalog # 44 79299; A-side Matrix # XSS 79299A
        - Nas - On the real, 2004; SR-22687; Nas (Box 368)
          Catalog # CAS 58391; A-side Matrix # XSS-58391A-1A
        - Nas - Nas is like; Dr. Knockboots, 1999; SR-22688; Nas (Box 368)
        - Nas - I am… (disc one), 1999; SR-22689; Nas; Puff Daddy; Aaliyah; DMX; Scarface (Box 368)
          In same jacket as # SR-22690. Double album.
          Catalog # C2S 41881; A-side Matrix # XSS-41882-A-1
        - Nas - I am… (disc two), 1999; SR-22690; Nas; Puff Daddy; Aaliyah; DMX; Scarface (Box 368)
          In same jacket as # SR-22689. Double album.
          Catalog # C2S 41881; A-side Matrix # XSS-41883-A-1
        - Nas - It was written, 1996; SR-22691; Nas; Firm; Hailey, Jo Jo; Hill, Lauryn (Box 368)
          Catalog # C 67015; A-side Matrix # AL-67015
        - Nas - Hate me now, 1999; SR-22692; Nas (Box 368)
          Catalog # CAS 41787; A-side Matrix # XSS 41787A
        - Nas - In too deep | The specialist, 1999; SR-22693; Nas; Nature; Vegas, Ali (Box 368)
          Catalog # 44 79216; A-side Matrix # XSS-79216-A
        - Nas - On the real | Coast II coast, 1997; SR-22701; Nas; Jac Swinga (Box 368)
          Catalog # UBLMT12; A-side Matrix # LMT 12 A
          Undaground Buttas
        - Nascimento, Milton - Courage, 1969; SR-22694; Nascimento, Milton (Box 368)
          Catalog # SA & M 2037; A-side Matrix # SP-3037
          A&M Records
          São Paulo, Brazil
        - Nascimento, Milton - Milton, 1976; SR-22695; Nascimento, Milton (Box 368)
          Catalog # SP-4611; A-side Matrix # 21925
        - Nastee Boyz - Killer b'z, 1986; SR-22696; Nastee Boyz (Box 368)
          Catalog # KOR 2272; A-side Matrix # KOR-2272-A
          Krossover Records
        - Nasty Habits - Round she goes, 1990; SR-22697; Nasty Habits (Box 368)
          Catalog # UJAM-1001; A-side Matrix # UJAM-1001-A
          U-Jam Records
          Plainfield, New Jersey
        - Nasty Habits - Round she goes, 1990; SR-22698; Nasty Habits (Box 368)
        - Nasty Habits - Shadow boxing; Prototyped, 1996; SR-22699; Nasty Habits (Box 368)
          Catalog # 31R-002; A-side Matrix # 31R-002 AA-1-1-1
          31 Records
          Berkshire, United Kingdom
        - Nasty Rox Inc. - Escape from New York, 1988; SR-22700; Nasty Rox Inc. (Box 368)
          Catalog # NROX1; A-side Matrix # NROX1A1
          ZTT
          United Kingdom
        - Nastyboy Klick - Tha 1st chapter (disc one), 1997; SR-22702; Nastyboy Klick (Box 368)
          In same jacket as # SR-22703. Double album. Annotated. Promo
          Catalog # MELP 159; A-side Matrix # MELP 159 1-A
          Mercury
        - Nastyboy Klick - Tha 1st chapter (disc two), 1997; SR-22703; Nastyboy Klick (Box 368)
          In same jacket as # SR-22702. Double album. Annotated. Promo
          Catalog # MELP 159; A-side Matrix # MELP 159 2-A
        - Nat - Go hard, 2001; SR-22704; Nat (Box 368)
          Catalog # UME-2001; A-side Matrix # UME-2001-A
          Upper Million Ent.
        - Natahlee - Weakness for sweetness, 1996; SR-22705; Natahlee; Oscar B (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22705. Different discs. Annotated. Promo. Not in discogs
          Catalog # SPRO-11642; A-side Matrix # SPRO-11642 4084-611642-1-3
        - Ursula 1000 - Boop, 2006; SR-22706; Ursula 1000; de Dominicis, Barbara; Ookawara, Izumi (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22706. Different discs.
          Catalog # ESL093; A-side Matrix # ESL-093-0510Y26
          Eighteenth Street Lounge Music
          Washington, DC
        - Natasha - Hold me, 1992; SR-22707; Natasha; Wilson, Natasha (Box 369)
          Catalog # GS 2369; A-side Matrix # GS 2369A
          Straker's Records
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Nate Dogg - Nobody does it better, 1998; SR-22708; Nate Dogg; Warren G. (Box 369)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # EPIC WARREN G & NATE DOGG-A
          Untertainment Records
        - Natural Beauty - Nice up dancee; You wanna be loved, 1986; SR-22709; Natural Beauty (Box 369)
          Catalog # RAS 7019; A-side Matrix # RAS 7019-A
          Ras Records
        - Native Rhythm - Paid my dues; Hey hey, 1993; SR-22710; Native Rhythm (Box 369)
          Catalog # DJ001AN; A-side Matrix # DJ 001-A
          Precision Kuttz
        - Native Tongue - Yowl, 1983; SR-22711; Native Tongue (Box 369)
          Catalog # MM020; A-side Matrix # MM-020-A
          Modern Method Records
          Boston, Massachusetts
        - Natural Elements - 2 tons; Live it up, 1999; SR-22712; Natural Elements (Box 369)
          Catalog # TB 495; A-side Matrix # TB 0495-A
          Tommy Boy Black Label
        - Natural Four - Heaven right here on Earth, 1995; SR-22713; Natural Four (Box 369)
          Catalog # CPLP 8155; A-side Matrix # CPLP8155A
          Charly Groove
        - Natural Four - Natural four, 1995; SR-22714; Natural Four (Box 369)
          Catalog # CPLP 8127; A-side Matrix # CPLP 8127A
        - Natural Mystics - Ain't so; How it go, 1996; SR-22715; Natural Mystics (Box 369)
          Catalog # DVE103; A-side Matrix # DVE103A
          Domestic Violence Entertainment
        - Natural Sequence - Leaving you, 1994; SR-22716; Natural Sequence; MC Master Dee (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22717. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FUNK1995; A-side Matrix # FUNK1995-A
          Funkmaster Records
        - Natural Sequence - Leaving you, 1994; SR-22717; Natural Sequence; MC Master Dee (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22716. 2 copies.
        - Nature Zone - Porcupine; Nobody can love me (like you do), 1976; SR-22718; Nature Zone (Box 369)
          Catalog # 5N - Disco 3000; A-side Matrix # ZCL 8150-12-X
          London Disco
        - Nature's Creation - Freak unique, 1985; SR-22719; Nature's Creation (Box 369)
          Catalog # CCR-123; A-side Matrix # CCR-000-A
          Capital City Records
        - Naughty By Nature - Nature's finest (Naughty By Nature's greatest hits) (disc one), 1999; SR-22720; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22721. Double album.
          Catalog # TB 1310; A-side Matrix # TB-1310-A
          Tommy Boy
        - Naughty By Nature - Nature's finest (Naughty By Nature's greatest hits) (disc two), 1999; SR-22721; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22720. Double album.
          Catalog # TB 1310; A-side Matrix # TB-1310-C
        - Naughty By Nature - Guard your grill; Uptown anthem, 1992; SR-22722; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          Catalog # TB 519; A-side Matrix # 1-519-A
        - Naughty By Nature - Naughty By Nature, 1991; SR-22723; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22724. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # TB 1044; A-side Matrix # TB-1044 A
        - Naughty By Nature - Naughty By Nature, 1991; SR-22724; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22723. 2 copies.Promo
        - Naughty By Nature - Mourn you til I join you, 1997; SR-22725; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22726. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TB 427; A-side Matrix # TB 427A
        - Naughty By Nature - Mourn you til I join you, 1997; SR-22726; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22725. 2 copies.
        - Naughty By Nature - Naughty by numbers, 1993; SR-22727; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          Catalog # TB 1079; A-side Matrix # TB 1079-A
        - Naughty By Nature - Craziest, 1995; SR-22728; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22729. 2 copies.Promo
          Catalog # TB 670; A-side Matrix # TB-670-1-A
        - Naughty By Nature - Craziest, 1995; SR-22729; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22728. 2 copies.Promo
        - Naughty By Nature - Nineteen naughty nine nature's fury (disc one), 1999; SR-22730; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22731. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # AL-9082; A-side Matrix # AL-9082-SA
          Arista
        - Naughty By Nature - Nineteen naughty nine nature's fury (disc two), 1999; SR-22731; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22730. Double album.Promo
          Catalog # AL-9082; A-side Matrix # AL-9082-SC
        - Naughty By Nature - Hip hop hooray; The hood comes first, 1993; SR-22732; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
          Catalog # TB 554; A-side Matrix # 1-554-B-A
        - Naughty By Nature - Naughty by numbers, 1993; SR-22733; Naughty By Nature (Box 369)
        - Nava, Mariella - Per paura o per amore, 1988; SR-22734; Nava, Mariella (Box 369)
          Catalog # PL 71665; A-side Matrix # PL71665A-25-1A3
          RCA Italiana
          Rome, Italy
        - Nay, Eric B. - Love don't love me, 1995; SR-22735; Nay, Eric B. (Box 369)
          No record company listed on the label or discogs
          Catalog # HTS-003; A-side Matrix # HTS-003-A
        - Nayobe - Guess I fell in love, 1987; SR-22736; Nayobe (Box 369)
          Catalog # SF 820 CLUB; A-side Matrix # SF 820 CLUB 1
          Fever Records
        - Nayobe | Konders, Bobby - All night long, 1995; SR-22737; Nayobe; Konders, Bobby; Fat Joe; Rayvon (Box 369)
          Catalog # WAR-172DJ; A-side Matrix # WAR-172-A
        - Nayobe - Please don't go, 1984; SR-22738; Nayobe (Box 369)
          Catalog # SF 802; A-side Matrix # SF-802-A
        - Nayobe - Please don't go, 1984; SR-22739; Nayobe (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22740. 2 copies.Promo
        - Nayobe - Please don't go, 1984; SR-22740; Nayobe (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22739. 2 copies.Promo
        - N.B. Hey - Da dribbol, 1996; SR-22741; N.B. Hey (Box 369)
          Catalog # PR12 7173-1WT; A-side Matrix # PR12 7172-1A
          Island Independent
        - N.C.S. - Real shaolin, 1996; SR-22742; N.C.S. (Box 369)
          Catalog # BPR1637; A-side Matrix # BPR-1637-A
          Black Prince Records
          Staten Island, New York
        - NdegéOcello, Me'Shell - Who is he and what is he to you, 1996; SR-22743; NdegéOcello, Me'Shell (Box 369)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8349-A; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8349-A-SR
        - NdegéOcello, Me'Shell - Dred loc, 1993; SR-22744; NdegéOcello, Me'Shell (Box 369)
          Catalog # PRO-A 6485; A-side Matrix # PRO A1-A2 6485-SR3
        - Ndour, Youssou - Djamil Inédits 84-85, 1985; SR-22745; Ndour, Youssou; N'Dour, Youssou (Box 369)
          Catalog # CEL 6809; A-side Matrix # CEL 6809-A
          Celluloid
          France
        - N'Dour, Youssou - 7 seconds, 1994; SR-22746; N'Dour, Youssou; Cherry, Neneh (Box 369)
          Catalog # 42 77482; A-side Matrix # 42-77482-A-1
          Chaos Recordings
        - N'Dour, Youssou - 7 seconds, 1994; SR-22747; N'Dour, Youssou; Cherry, Neneh (Box 369)
        - N'Dour, Youssou - The rubberband man, 1986; SR-22748; N'Dour, Youssou (Box 369)
          Catalog # ET 004; A-side Matrix # ET 004 A-1U-1-1
          Rough Trade
        - Ne-Yo - Because of you (disc one), 2007; SR-22749; Ne-Yo; Jay-Z; Hudson, Jennifer (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22750. Double album.
          Catalog # B0008697-01; A-side Matrix # B0008697-01-LP1A
          Island Def Jam Music Group
        - Ne-Yo - Because of you (disc two), 2007; SR-22750; Ne-Yo; Jay-Z; Hudson, Jennifer (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22749. Double album.
          Catalog # B0008697-01; A-side Matrix # B0008697-01-LP2A
        - Ne-Yo - When you're mad, 2006; SR-22751; Ne-Yo; LL Cool J (Box 369)
          Catalog # DEFR 16494-1; A-side Matrix # B0006318-11A
          Def Jam Recordings
        - Ne-Yo - Stay, 2005; SR-22752; Ne-Yo; Peedi Peedi (Box 369)
          Catalog # DEFR 16327-1; A-side Matrix # B0004892-11-A
        - Ne-Yo - In my own words sampler, 2006; SR-22753; Ne-Yo; Peedi Peedi (Box 369)
          Catalog # DEFF 16541-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16541-1A
        - Ne-Yo - Stay, 2005; SR-22754; Ne-Yo; Peedi Peedi (Box 369)
        - Ne-Yo - When you're mad, 2006; SR-22755; Ne-Yo; LL Cool J (Box 369)
        - Ne-Yo - So sick, 2005; SR-22756; Ne-Yo (Box 369)
          Catalog # DEFR 16455-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16455-1A
        - Nearly God - Poems, 1996; SR-22757; Nearly God (Box 369)
          Catalog # 12DP 003 DJ; A-side Matrix # 12 DP 003
          Durban Poison
        - Nebula - Nebula 1, 1988; SR-22758; Nebula (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22759. 2 copies.
          Catalog # GEE 12002; A-side Matrix # GEE-12-002-A
          G-Zone
        - Nebula - Nebula 1, 1988; SR-22759; Nebula (Box 369)
          In same jacket as # SR-22758. 2 copies.
        - Nebula - Nebula 1, 1988; SR-22760; Nebula (Box 369)